Today my roommate got himself insulted in the market.  The
shop owner was also
laughing so much, I can't even tell you.  So today I am going to the
market with both my roommates.  So as soon as you reach the market.   First of all
I ate pineapple because
I was very hungry.
After that I saw some clothes.
I was very confused with these two jeans as to
which one I should buy.  But the size was not available
so I did not buy any.  Then my
roommate falls in the middle of a crowded gathering and
everyone makes fun of her.  But we
explained it to him and went around the market.
Then we also visited the sleeper shop.  But
we didn't like anything.  So I reached there to
eat Falooda.  First of all I drank almond
shake which was much tastier than my expectations.
Then I
ate Falooda.  Its name is something like Rabri Falooda
which was turning out to be so tasty.
What can I say?  Next time I
go to the market, I will definitely
eat this again.  Then, feeling tired and exhausted, I reached the
PG.  I quickly changed my clothes
and sat down to eat.  I made bottle gourd today.   I was
not feeling well.  So I
thought it best to eat something light and I did
video editing till 2:00 in the night.  So I was craving something
sweet so I ordered waffles.
Love you.  Bye.